tokyocheapo.com 2019-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Tokyo Cheapo

Last updated: July 19th, 2018.

This policy explains how we collect and treat any information you give us. We comply with the [General Data Protection Regulations](https://www.eugdpr.org/), the [California Online Privacy Protection Act](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Online_Privacy_Protection_Act) (CalOPPA) and the [CAN SPAM Act](https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/guidance/can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business).

## The Tokyo Cheapo privacy policy covers

  * Ways that we collect information
  * What information we hold
  * How and where we store your information
  * What we use your information for
  * Third party services that we use
  * Who’s responsible for your information at our company
  * Who has access to information about you
  * The steps we take to keep your information private
  * How to make a complaint
  * CalOPPA specific provisions
  * CAN SPAM Act provisions
  * Changes to the policy

## Ways that we collect information

We collect contact information including your name, email address, phone number, and address on our website only for handling enquiries, fulfilling information requests, receiving bookings and taking orders.

We collect your email address, name (when provided) and the country in which you are located when you sign up for one of our newsletters.

We track users to our site with cookies (cookies are a small piece of data stored in your web browser when you visit our website [read more here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie)). Cookies are not connected to any other information that you might submit to us such as email addresses, names, addresses or any other personally identifiable information.

## What information we hold

When you contact us by email or through our website, we collect your name, email address, phone number and company (if you provide this).

When you buy or order something from us, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, billing address, passport number, flight information, travel dates and ports of entry and exit from the country.

If you do business with us, we also collect your business name, bank details and we keep records of the invoices we send you and the payments you make.

Purchases through the website are processed by our payment providers Stripe or PayPal. We have no access to your credit card information.

## Where we store your information

When you contact us by email or through our website, your information is stored on our email server or in Gmail – a service offered by Google. If you are a business client of ours, we store your information in our Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software, in our own accounts software and on Google Drive. If you sign up for a newsletter, we store your email address, name and the country in which you are located in MailChimp (mailchimp.com). When you buy, order or reserve something, your information is stored in our database and (when payment is made through the site) with our payment provider. All third party services use best practice security and we use strong passwords when we access them.

## What we use your information for

We use the information you give us to send you newsletters which include news about our site and also offers from our advertising partners. You have the option to unsubscribe from any and all communication. All automated email communication includes “unsubscribe” links so that you can stop receiving communication from us.

We also use your information to complete orders, purchases and requests. If an order or purchase requires fulfillment by a third party vendor, we pass your information to that third party. We only pass on personally identifiable information to third parties that is required in order to complete the purchase, order or enquiry. No payment or credit card information is passed to third parties.

For allowing our visitors to buy or order certain products or services (such as concert tickets), we use some third party ordering systems. We collect information necessary to fullfil your order as does the third party provider.

Additionally, we use our own and third party cookies to serve ads and track site usage. All cookie data is anonymized and contains no personally identifiable information such as name, email address, gender, age or postal address. Information collected through cookies may include information such as general location, IP address, pages visited, browser version and the type of device that you are viewing our site on.

Our site is free for all to use because we receive income from ad revenue. tracking through cookies helps us to improve the experience of using the site and to adapt the content to you depending on your usage and locations. For example, we can display prices in your local currency and we can stop a notice appearing to you on each page if you have already dismissed it once.

## Third party services that we use

We use DoubleClick by Google to manage and serve ads. You can visit their site [here](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) and you can see the Google Privacy Policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).  
We use [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/features/marketing-automation/) to manage email lists and campaigns. Their privacy policy is [here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).  
We use Google Analytics to track site usage so that we can improve the site experience and develop new articles and content. You can wiew the Google Privacy Policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).  
We use [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) and [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/) for receiving payments. You can find the Stripe Privacy Policy [here](https://stripe.com/privacy) and the PayPal privacy policy [here](https://www.paypal.com/hk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).  
We use Sojern and Adara to collect data for serving ads and to obtain user insights for improving the site experience and develop new articles and content. Sojern’s privacy policy is [here](https://www.sojern.com/privacy/). Adara’s privacy policy is [here](https://adara.com/privacy-promise/).  
For ordering of some concert and event tickets, we use [Zaiko](http://zaiko.io/en/). You can see their privacy policy [here](https://iflyer.tv/en-jp/about/legal/).

## Who’s responsible for your information at our company

Greg Lane, our CTO, is responsible for the security of your information. You can contact him by email at greg.lane@fasttrainltd.com if you have any concerns about the information we store.

## Who has access to information about you

When we store information in our own systems, only the people who need it have access. Our management team have access to everything you’ve provided, but individual employees have access to only what they need to do their job.

## The steps we take to keep your information private

All pages on our site are sent to your web browser over a secure, encrypted “https” connection. All data submitted through our site and to third party services is also transmitted over a secure, encrypted connection.

Where we store your information on third-party services, we restrict access only to people who need it. We use different randomly generated passwords for each service, and we never use the same password twice.

## How to complain

We take complaints very seriously. If you’ve any reason to complain about the ways we handle your privacy, please contact Greg Lane by email at greg.lane [ put at mark here ] fasttrainltd.com or by post to Fast Train Ltd., 9-2-13 Akasaka, Minato-ku, Japan

## CalOPPA Specific Provisions

### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:  
By logging in to their account

### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

We do not allow

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

We do not specifically market to children under 13

### Fair Information Practices

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**  
We will notify the users via email within 7 business days

We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors

## CAN SPAM Act

### We collect your email address:

To send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  
To market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

### To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

We will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses  
We will identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way  
We will include the physical address of our business or site headquarters  
We will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly  
We will give an ‘opt-out’ or ‘unsubscribe’ option

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can**  
Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

## Changes to the policy

If we change the contents of this policy, those changes will become effective the moment we publish them on our website.
